[{"answer": "We were hearing loud booms, loud blasts, a lot of rapid gunfire.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "Sara, if you can hear me, I know there's been problems with communication here, what is the latest there right now?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, what we are hearing from the rebels is that, yes, they had hold of all three of the sons and now, they're saying hold on, Mohammed -- one of his sons -- Mohammed Gadhafi has escaped.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes, it's difficult to say in this place, isn't it, because one correspondent who's been here much longer than me said that, you know, the thing is about Libya, the trouble with reporting it is that lying is the national sport.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Do you actually believe that either of these sons were ever in proper custody or were we just spun a yarn here?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Well, I think the capital of Tripoli is mostly under the control of the revolutionary forces.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Do you think he's still there?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, there is a lot of confusion, a lot of misinformation going on here.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "What do you make of what's going on?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "SLAN: It's hard to imagine a scenario whereby the Gadhafi loyalists manage to actually regain control over Tripoli, let alone over the entire country.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Do you feel that Moammar Gadhafi's position is basically over and we're just watching the beginning of the end?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "And the situation, of course, is much worse in Libya than it was in Egypt where you had at least the centralized military that could really form the backbone of a post-revolutionary society.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "What is going to happen in Libya to reassure the world that we're actually into a better situation for Libyan people?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Under no circumstances is that going to happen.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Can you see a situation where if it gets completely out of control, though, the Americans will have to go in more harder and more people on the ground?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Yes, we've talked about this before, you and I.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Do you have any credence to those kinds of reports?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "I mean with the rebels in control of from what I understand some 80 percent of the capital city of Tripoli, it's only a matter of time.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "When is Gadhafi going to be gone, do you think, looking at the situation as it is now?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Well, this is a very fluid situation.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Were you disheartened to hear that two of Gadhafi's sons, having been in some form of custody, are now liberated again and are no longer in custody?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Moammar Gadhafi should be brought to justice and I think that it's important that the U.S. government does not try to broker a deal to find him asylum or grant him immunity, but he should be adjudicated either in the Libyan -- in the Libyan judicial system that needs to be revamped or with the international criminal court.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "If you had a choice in the way that the American SEALs had a choice with Osama bin Laden of killing Moammar Gadhafi or bringing him back to justice, which would you prefer?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I'm already questioning your judgment.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Are you questioning by judgment or what?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Preeminence with the United States.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What is the Jon Huntsman for America?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Can it be the same as it used to be?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "The American dream is the same.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Or should the American dream be slightly reinvented for the modern world?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "And you were in China for a couple of years and you well know that when you compared bureaucracy in China to bureaucracy in America, one of the reasons that they are marching on, good or bad, whatever your view of it, is they are not consumed with red tape over every tiny thing they do.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Why try to build something like they did the last generation?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "In an autocratic system like China, there's plenty of red tape.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "But does America have a fundamental problem businesswise with the sheer volume of paperwork, red tape, legalese, stuff that I believe slows down modern business?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "I'll disabuse them of that real fast.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Other than people saying you're boring?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Hard work.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "What values did he instill in you?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Well, we had a lot of bands.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "What was the name of your band?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Donnie and Marie did OK.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Did you see a potential conflict arising had you pursued your dream?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "If you can tell me anything about Captain Beefheart, I'll give you an answer.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Now is that true?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "We've come this far.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Do you want to get your hands dirty in the grubbiness of running for high office and all that comes with it?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "They have been raised in a public milieu, a public environment.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Are you comfortable that they're ready?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Well, it's early days.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Why is that and how do you change that?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Not August.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "When is the point when we should look at how you're performing and properly judge you?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "I do, yes.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "You really want to get me in trouble, do you?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "I don't -- well, I tell you what I've told most people, if not everybody.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "What's the one that you would say to a friend over dinner?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "He appointed me and I stood up and took the appointment to serve my country.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Do you have sympathy for him in the position he found himself in, where you have such an intransigent part of the republican party really just refusing to compromise?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Well, on the debt ceiling.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Where would you disagree with her?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "On gay marriage?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "I am pro-life.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "What is your view of abortion?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Rape, incest and life of the mother would be the exceptions that I could live with.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Do you think there are any circumstances where you would think an abortion is acceptable?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "All I have to say -- I don't have a lot of patience on a lot of the non-economic issues.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "When you see, again, intransigence by some of the -- particularly the Tea Party end of the Republican party on this kind of thing, do you think again that it's bordering on bigotry?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Would you endorse what he said?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "I don't know him that well.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Do you like him?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I'm just pointing out the facts.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "But what you're basically doing is knifing him straight in the back, aren't you?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I'm glad to get your endorsement, Piers.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "But what I'm saying is you clearly have it in you?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "There would be too many jokes about that.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Could you ever imagine running as a running mate to someone like Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "You know, anyone who is going to --", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "What about to a Tea Party candidate?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Captain Beefheart music, I assume you're talking.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Could you countenance such an idea?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Everybody knows -- I think they're rewarded by people who they elect and put into Congress.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Shouldn't they be rewarded with a seat at the right hand?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "I'm not playing the name game at all.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "You wouldn't rule out Michele Bachmann?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "The situation now is pretty calm.", "docId": "110822pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "What is the situation?", "qSentId": 580}]